It looks really embarrassing.
すごい恥ずかしそうです
It's hard to say this important thing.
この大切な言いにくいからさ
I thought for a moment that the rice balls wouldn't fall.
ちょっと おにぎり落ちないなって思って
About this.
こっちについて
To this side.
こっちの方にさ
Here's a small one.
ここに小さいのを
About the waist.
腰について
Ah, that's good.
あー いいっすね
That's how your waist is.
腰をそうで
The reaction was great.
すっごい反応良かった
It was a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしかった
Sorry.
ごめんね
It's kind of cute.
なんか可愛いって
Her reaction just now is cute.
今の反応可愛くて
I want you to sleep.
寝てほしい
I was surprised.
びっくりしちゃったね
It hurts when I sleep.
寝ると苦しい
I like it and it's warm.
気に入って温かいね
what happened?
どうしたの?
It felt a little good.
ちょっと気持ちよくて
I couldn't do much.
あ ん まりできなかった
Can I put it in?
入れてもいい?
Kobabanko feels good.
コババンコ気持ちいい
I got it all in.
すっごい全部入っちゃった
Even Koba Banco has entered.
コババンコまで入っちゃってる
Please be careful.
気 を つ けてください
Feels good
気 持ちよす
Gite.
ぎ て
I did it live.
生でやっちゃったもんね
Sorry, sorry.
ごめんごめん
It felt good.
気持ちよかったし
We're going to have sex again.
またセックスしちゃう